ELLA LOH

UX/UI DESIGNER







EDUCATION

UX Design

Certificate, 2020 CareerFoundry.com

Fashion Design

Certificate, 2015-2016 NYSD

International Relations

Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), 2008-2011 Boston University

Visual Arts

Minor, 2008-2011 Boston University

UX SKILLS

User Research

Affinity Mapping
Competitive Analysis
Journey Mapping
A/B & Preference Testing
Usability Testing
User Personas

Design

Design Systems
Information Architecture
Prototyping
Lo - Hi-Fi Wireframing
User Personas
User Interface Design
HTML/CSS

TOOLS

Figma
Sketch
InVision & Marvel
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe XD

PROFILE

UX/UI Designer with a background in Fashion. Experienced in large-scale product development, strategy and solving design problems while communicating with a variety of international clients, geographically distributed colleagues and vendors with different shipping requirements. Driven by cross-team collaboration, user-centric, engaging and appealing user experiences in the San Francisco Bay Area.

EXPERIENCE

Product Designer - UX/UI

2020-present

B STEM - Remote

- Conduct user research on a team of designers while relying on the importance of data in those decisions to iterate user flows from low-fidelity to interactive prototypes using Figma, Photoshop and InVision
- Contribute to high-level strategic decisions with the rest of the product and executive teams throughout the product lifecycle to address user and business needs are feasible to implement, and are subsequently implemented accurately
- Drive the development and communication of clear design guidelines, patterns and libraries to reduce visual complexity of the product

Visual Designer

2018-2020

Freelance - Paris, France

 Work with clients on a project-to-project basis to create Keynote infographics and presentations for clients like Johnson & Johnson

Associate Designer

2016-2018

JA/EG - New York, NY

- Responsible for R&D including shopping stores, competitive analysis, inspirational images that translates to trend design presentations and new concepts for the Kid's line
- Generate a 13-17% increase in revenue by managing the Kids' spec packages for factories and customer presentations including drawing on Adobe Photoshop and Illustrator, approval of samples, reporting directly to the Art Director
- Reduce team mistakes by coordinating a set color palette and CAD dimensions resulting in 20 hours of time saving per month

Supervisor 2013-2016

Uniqlo USA - San Jose, CA/New York, NY

- Grow and communicate with staff of 80, promoting four to DA's and two to SV's to ensure toward achievement of sales targets, inventory levels, and cash management
- Create system for submitting new designs, winning the first round in the USA and subsequently seeing that same design on the floor two seasons later
- Plan and execute store layout by working with the GM and AM, consistently having top sales in the Bay Area for two years including analyzing weekly allocation and inventory control, reducing missing SKU's to 4% or less for four months